

SHAILY GANDHI

UX/UI designer

⊕ shaily.design

CONTACT

shailymgandhi@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/shaily-gandhi

+31 6 84480755

O Hoofddorp, NL

SKILLS

UX design
UI design
Prototyping and Wireframing
Problem solving
User research
User interviews & testing

TOOLS

Figma / Sketch / Miro / Adobe XD / Photoshop

EDUCATION

UX/UI Bootcamp Ironhack, Amsterdam 2021 - 2022

Bachelors of Architecture CEPT University, Ahmedabad 2007 - 2013

Student Exchange Program TUM, Munich. 2011

PROFILE

I am an Architect turned UX-UI designer with 7+ years of experience in Design industry.

I am dedicated to work towards achieving goals and to carefully create products that bring positive change into people's lives. My approach to design is grounded in user research & human experience to solve the **small but significant** problems, both for users & businesses.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UX/UI Designer

Tellow, Amsterdam

July 2022 - Current

May 2022 - June 2022 (UX-UI design Internship)

- Translate complex issues into a clear story to improve lives of 50k users
- Increased Tellow app usage by designing a new feature page for marketing website
- Provide conceptual and strategic advice on product development
- Develop user flows, create wireframes and deliver hi-fi prototypes
- Use research methods to analyze the users and understand the business needs
- Setting up the design system and component library

UX/UI Design

Ironhack, Amsterdam

September 2021 - April 2022

- UX-UI design of a travel app- Motuu
 (Collaboration with a client, UX research, Wireframing, High Fidelity Prototype, Usability Testing, Desirability Testing, Style Guide)
- Design of a native ios Nutrition checking app
 Wireframing, High Fidelity Prototype, Usability Testing, Desirability Testing,
 Stylequide
- Editorial Design, Design of a responsive Web Magazine
 UX/UI Design, UX Research, Usability Testing, Responsive Design Guide

Assistant Designer

KENK Architecten B.V., Amsterdam

April 2018 - October 2020

Associate Architect

Keystone Architects, Bangalore

November 2015 - September 2017